<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on lipu pi soweli Niko</title>
    <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on lipu pi soweli Niko</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020 nihilazo</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.itwont.work/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Easy Mushroom Soup</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/mushroomsoup.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/mushroomsoup.html</guid>
      <description>Serves 4 (as a starter soup), 2 (as a main)
Ingredients 125g onion, chopped 225g mushrooms, sliced oil for cooking 25g plain flour 300ml nondairy milk of your choice 450ml vegetable stock mixed herbs to taste salt and pepper to taste Method Cook the onion and mushrooms in a pan until soft. stir in the flour to form a paste, gradually add the milk and stock. stir in the herbs, salt, and better, and cook for 10-ish minutes blend and cook for a further 5 minutes Notes this is a meh mushroom soup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creamy Spinach and Mushroom Pasta</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/mushroompasta.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/mushroompasta.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 175g pasta (I used penne) 50g unroasted, unsalted cashews 10g dried porcini mushrooms 1 veg stock cube 1 tbsp of a neutral oil 120g chestnut mushrooms, halved if large, thinly sliced 2 large garlic cloves, finely grated 200g baby spinach Method Cook the penne following pack instructions and put the kettle on to boil. Meanwhile, put the cashews and dried mushrooms in a medium heatproof bowl along with the bouillon powder, and pour over 200ml boiling water from the kettle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Bean Burgers</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/beanburgers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/beanburgers.html</guid>
      <description>Makes 6 Burgers
Ingredients 1 can black beans, drained 60g Vital Wheat Gluten 20g Breadcrumbs 1tsp Chili Powder 1/2tsp Ground Cumin 60ml water 1tsp ketchup 2 cloves garlic (or equivalent garlic powder) 1/2 small onion Method Mash the beans with a fork in a mixing bowl.
Add the vital wheat gluten, breadcrumbs, chili powder, cumin, water, and ketchup. press and add the garlic, mince or grate the onion and add.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheat Chili</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/chili.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/chili.html</guid>
      <description>Serves 3-4
Ingredients 1 Onion, chopped 500g Vegan Mince ~200ml Vegetable Stock 1 1/2 tsp Chili Powder 1 can Chopped Tomatoes A squirt of tomato puree 1 can Red Beans in Chili Sauce Oil (for frying) Method Fry onion in a saucepan until soft.
Add mince and stock. Cook until brown.
Add chopped tomatoes, tomato puree, and chili powder. Simmer for 10 minutes.
Add red beans in chili sauce.
Simmer for 15 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheat Korma</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/korma.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/korma.html</guid>
      <description>Serves 3-4
Ingredients 1 Onion, chopped 2tsp Ground Ginger 1/2 Jar Korma Spice Paste 50ml Water 500g Mock Meat Pieces (like vegan Quorn or similar) 1 can Chickpeas, Drained 1 can Coconut Milk 1 can Lentils, Drained Oil (for frying) Method Fry onion in a saucepan until soft.
Add ground ginger and spice paste. Cook for 2 minutes.
Add 50ml water and cook until evaporated.
Add mock meat pieces and cook until browned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chickpea Masala</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/chickpeamasala.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/chickpeamasala.html</guid>
      <description>Serves 4-6
Ingredients Oil, for frying 1 onion, diced 1 yellow pepper, deseeded and finely chopped 2 garlic cloves, finely chopped 2 tsp garam masala 1 tsp ground cumin 1/2 tsp ground tumeric 2 carrots, peeled and finely chopped 2 400g cans of chickpeas, drained 2 400g cans of chopped tomatoes 1 400g can of coconut milk 1/4tsp cayenne pepper salt, to taste Method Heat enough oil to coat the bottom of a large saucepan over a medium-high heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chickpea Salad</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/chickpea-salad.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/chickpea-salad.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 250 g chickpeas, cooked 60g veganaise 5g bull kelp powder 2 pickled cucumbers 1.25 g cayenne pepper powder Method Cook 125 g (3/4 cup) of dried chickpeas (see instructions), or use 1 can (15oz). Mash chickpeas down with a fork.
Mix the mashed chickpeas with 60 g (3-4 tbsp) of venagaise, 15 g (1 tsp) bull kelp powder, 2 chopped pickles and 1.25 g (1/4 tsp) of cayenne pepper powder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate Brownies</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/brownies.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/brownies.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 140 grams (1 cup) plain flour 20 grams (1/4 cup) cocoa powder 200 grams (1 cup) caster sugar 80 ml (1/3 cup) vegetable oil 1 teaspoon vanilla extract 200 grams (1/2 cup) dairy free (vegan) dark chocolate, melted 240 ml (1 cup) Oat Milk 75 grams (1/2 cup) dairy free (vegan) chocolate chips, optional Method Preheat oven to 180 C (350 F) standard / 160 C (320 F) fan-forced. Line an 8-inch square baking tin with baking or parchment paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flapjack</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/flapjack.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/flapjack.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 210g Margerine/Vegan Butter 210g Light Brown Sugar 160g Golden Syrup 350g Oats 100g sultanas (or other dried fruits) Method Preheat an oven to 160C
Line a tray bake tin with greaseproof paper
Melt the margerine, syrup, and sugar together in a large saucepan and combine
Add the oats and fruit and mix well
Pour into the tray bake tin and press down to make even
Bake for 20 minutes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kvass</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/kvass.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/kvass.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 450g rye bread, sliced (stale or fresh) 3.5l water 1 tablespoon rye starter (optional) 1 1/2 teaspoons champaigne years or 1/2 teaspoon active dry yeast 85g golden syrup (originally honey, but I&amp;rsquo;m veganifying this) 95g plus 1/2 teaspoon sugar 1 raisin About 8 small sprigs of fresh mint (I left these out) Method Preheat the oven to 200C. Place the bread onto the oven rack and let bake for until well toasted and completely firm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lemon Sorbet</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/lemon_sorbet.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/lemon_sorbet.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 225g/8oz caster sugar 6 unwaxed lemons Method Tip the caster sugar into a saucepan and add 250ml water. Bring slowly to the boil, stirring to dissolve the sugar. Boil for 2 minutes and then remove from the heat.
Finely grate the zest from 3 of the lemons and add to the sugar syrup. Cut all of the lemons in half and squeeze the juice - you should end up with about 225ml/8fl oz of juice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Lentil Daal</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/lentildaal.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/lentildaal.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Olive oil for frying 2 onions, finely sliced 3 garlic cloves, finely chopped 2.5cm piece of ginger, grated (or use ground ginger) 2tsp ground cumin 1tsp ground tumeric 1tsp ground coriander 1/2tsp garam masala 1/4tsp cayenne pepper 1 400g can of chopped tomatoes 270g dry red lentils 2 carrots, diced salt and pepper to taste Method Heat enough oil to cover the bottom of a large pan over medium-high heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Lentil Stew</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/redlentilstew.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/redlentilstew.html</guid>
      <description>Serves 2
Ingredients 1tbsp olive oil (for cooking) 1 medium onion 1/4 tsp black pepper 1/2 tsp cumin seeds 1/4 tsp ground tumeric 1 carrot 2 medium potatoes 1/4 head green cabbage (or other veg) a pinch of salt 100g red lentils 350ml vegetable stock Method Heat a pot at medium heat, then coat bottom with olive oil. Add onion, sautée for 5 minutes. Add black pepper, cumin seeds and turmeric.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roasted Cashews</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/roasted_cashews.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/roasted_cashews.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 lb (0.45kg) Whole Cashews 2/3 tsp (10/15 ml) oil Salt and pepper (to taste) Method Preheat oven to 180 degrees. Add cashews to large baking tray (lined or not).
Spread the cashews in an even layer in the baking tray.
Drizzle 1/2 tsp of oil over the cashews and toss to evenly coat.
Roast on the middle rack of the oven for 5 minutes.
Remove from the oven and stir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet&amp;Sour Chickpea Rice Bowl</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/sweet_sour_chickpea_rice_bowl.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/sweet_sour_chickpea_rice_bowl.html</guid>
      <description>Serves: 1
Ingredients 1-2 servings of cooked rice (google says one serving is around 1/3 cup = 70g uncooked rice per person) 1 red onion 1 bell pepper or 2-3 tiny ones 1 small piece of fresh ginger (around 2.5cm) or ground ginger oil for the pan 1 tbsp cornstarch 2 tbsp water 1 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp ketchup hot sauce to taste (I added 1/2 tsp) 2 tsp rice syrup (mirin) or alternative sweet syrup 2 tbsp white wine vinegar 1 tbsp tomato puree 1/2 can chickpeas (120g; 4,23oz) extra water to adjust the consistency sesame seeds; spring onion for serving Method Cook the rice according to the packet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vanilla ice cream base</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/icecream.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/icecream.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 235ml nondairy milk 150g silken tofu 1 tbsp vanilla extract 100g cream from the top of a can of coconut milk 150g sugar Method combine all ingredients in the bowl of a blender or food processor and blend until smooth
transfer to ice cream maker and follow manufacturer&amp;rsquo;s instructions
Transfer to plastic container and freeze
Notes You can eat this as a vanilla ice cream or add/top with whatever extra flavours you want!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vegan chocolate cookies</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/cookies.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/cookies.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 250 grams all-purpose flour 1 teaspoon baking powder 3/4 teaspoon baking soda 1/2 teaspoon fine salt 1 1/4 cups dark chocolate chips (or guess) 100 grams sugar 110 grams packed light or dark brown sugar 140ml canola, grapeseed, or any other neutral oil 75ml water Coarse-grained sea salt or flaky sea salt, for garnish Method In a large bowl, whisk together flour, baking powder, baking soda, and salt. Add the chocolate chips to the flour mixture and toss to coat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegan Cinnamon Rolls</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/cinnamonrolls.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/cinnamonrolls.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients For the Dough 40g vegan butter 1 packet instant yeast (or use rapid-rise yeast // 1 packet yields ~ 2 1/4 tsp) 240 ml unsweetened nondairy milk 1 tbsp sugar 1/4 tsp salt 400 g unbleached all-purpose flour For the Filling 42 g vegan butter, melted 50 g organic cane sugar 1 1/2 to 3 tsp ground cinnamon (to taste) For the Topping 30 g vegan butter, melted Method In a large sauce pan (or in a bowl in the microwave at 30-second increments), heat the milk and butter until warm and melted, never reaching boiling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegan Lime Pies</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/limepies.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/limepies.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 190 g vegan graham cracker or digestive biscuit crumbs 60 g vegan butter (melted // such as Earth Balance) 120 g raw cashews (soaked for 4-6 hours or overnight, then drained) 180 ml light or full-fat coconut milk (well shaken) 60 ml coconut oil (melted) 3-4 large limes, juiced (3-4 limes yield ~1/2 cup juice) 1 Tbsp lime zest 80-120 ml agave nectar/maple syrup (depending on preferred sweetness) Method Preheat oven to 375 degrees F (190 C) and line a standard muffin tin with 12 paper liners (as original recipe is written // adjust if altering batch size).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veganaise</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/veganaise.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/veganaise.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 250g soft tofu 60ml canola oil 15ml apple cider vinegar 30g dijon mustard 1.25g salt Method Place the 250 g (1 cup) of soft tofu, 15 ml (1 tbsp) apple cider vinegar, 30 g (2 tbsp) dijon mustard and 1.25 g (1/4 tsp) salt in a blender and process until smooth. Add 60 ml (4 tbsp) of canola oil, and continue to blend for 1-2 minutes. Notes Source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegetable Paella</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/paella.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/paella.html</guid>
      <description>Serves 4-6
Ingredients 4 tablespoons olive oil 2 onions, chopped 2 garlic cloves, chopped 1 red pepper, seeded and sliced 1 yellow pepper, seeded and sliced 450g tomatoes, skinned and chopped 225g green beans, trimmed 450g peas in pods 450g arborio rice 1 tsp paprika 300ml dry white wine 1/2 tsp saffron 900ml veg stock salt and peppr Method Heat the olive oil in a large pan. Fry the onion and garlic until soft and golden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waffles</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/waffles.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/waffles.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 470ml nondairy milk 1 tbsp cornstarch 1 tbsp cider vinegar 350g plain flour 45g sugar 1 tbsp baking powder 1/2 tsp salt 75ml water 2 tbsp canola, corn, or another neutral oil, plus oil for waffle iron 1 tsp vanilla Method In a measuring jug, use a fork to mix half the milk with the cornstarch until fully dissolved. Add the remaining milk and the vinegar and set aside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walnut Granola</title>
      <link>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/granola.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itwont.work/recipes/granola.html</guid>
      <description>Walnut Granola Ingredients 90g Oats 115g Walnuts 1tsp Cinnamon 2tbsp Melted Coconut Oil 60ml Maple Syrup 2tbsp Almond Butter Sea Salt to taste Method Heat your oven to 150C/140C fan. Line a baking tray with parchment paper.
Combine oats, walnuts, cinnamon, and salt in a bowl.
Drizzle over maple syrup and melted coconut oil.
Add almond butter and stir.
Place onto baking sheet and press until about 1&amp;quot; thick overall. Bake for 15 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
